AegisOps Autopilot is a Track 4 production incident autopilot for Qwen Cloud.
It turns ambiguous alerts into memory-backed diagnosis, tool evidence, and reversible remediation.
The checkout workflow shows incident context, persistent operational memory, and Qwen-backed reasoning.
Human approval gates pause unsafe production mutation while preserving the audit trail.
The same five incident tools are exposed through Qwen Function Calling, OpenAPI, and MCP stdio.
The dashboard maps the official 30/30/25/15 rubric to concrete repository evidence.
Deterministic evals and ablations verify the full workflow against a single-agent baseline.
The full workflow scores 0.988, compared with 0.420 for the weaker baseline.
Alibaba deployment proof and verification scripts are included without exposing secrets.
Judges can run the project through StackBlitz, GitHub Pages, or a local clone.